Suheer Zahid

0332 4700802· suheer.work18@gmail.com Lahore Medical Housing Society, Harbasnpura, Lahore,

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

A motivated Full Stack Developer with 1+ years of experience, having strong command over HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Highly experienced in developing websites and web applications with Bootstrap, Tailwind, React JS and Node JS. Adept in developing user interfaces, testing and debugging applications. Possesses excellent analytical and problem-solving skills to debug code quickly and effectively.

STRENGTHS & SKILLS

React JSNode JSHTML 5Tailwind CSSRedux ToolkitAPI IntegrationCSS 3BootstrapRest APIResponsive DesignJavaScriptMaterial UI

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

IT Experts International Full Stack Developer

Oct 2024 - Present

As a MERN Stack Developer at IT Experts International in Pakistan, I was responsible for designing and developing full-stack web applications using the MERN (MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js) stack. This role allowed me to utilize my skills in front-end and back-end development to create dynamic and user-friendly websites.

Social Swirl Aug 2023 - Oct 2023

React JS Developer

As a React JS Developer at Social Swirl in Pakistan from August 2023 to October 2023, I was responsible for creating and maintaining high-quality web applications using React JS. During my time at Social Swirl, I gained valuable experience in developing user-friendly interfaces and optimizing website performance through efficient coding practices.

PORTFOLIO

https://suheer.vercel.app

SKILLS

Strong Communication

Results-Oriented
Time Management

Problem-Solving Design Thinking

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Computer Science

Virtual University of Pakistan

The intermediate of Computer Science

Al-Noorian College Lahore

Matric

Modern Standard School, Lahore

PROJECTS

Ecommerce Website

LMS Website

portfolio Website

IT Experts Main Website

https://itexpertsofficial.com

GitHub Repos Links

https://github.com/CodeWithSuheer?tab=repositories